<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
<title>Bridgewater - Daily Observations</title>
<link>https://henix.github.io/feeds/bwdo/</link>
<description></description>
<language>zh-cn</language>
<lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 16:43:46 +0800</lastBuildDate>
<item>
<title>Chinese-American Misunderstandings, Disputes, and Wars</title>
<link>https://henix.github.io/feeds/bwdo/2018-06-18-bwam06182018.html</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bridgewater.com/resources/bwam06182018.pdf&quot;&gt;原文&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In these &lt;i&gt;Observations,&lt;/i&gt; Ray Dalio shares his thoughts on the evolving trade dispute between China and the US, and the fundamental differences in values and approaches that lie beneath the conflict.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<author>Bridgewater</author>
<guid isPermaLink="false">2018-06-18-bwam06182018</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>A Top-Down Look at the Chinese Equity Market</title>
<link>https://henix.github.io/feeds/bwdo/2018-04-19-bwam04192018.html</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bridgewater.com/resources/bwam04192018.pdf&quot;&gt;原文&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Within a decade or so there is a high likelihood that the Chinese equity market will be on par with the US and European equity markets in terms of its size and importance to global investors. With this in mind, a top-down view of the Chinese equity market in relation to the US and Europe shows similarities in their fundamental drivers and important differences in how things are playing out.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<author>Bridgewater</author>
<guid isPermaLink="false">2018-04-19-bwam04192018</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Inclusion of China in Bloomberg’s Global Aggregate Bond Index Boosts Pressure on Investors to Figure Out How They Will Deal with the Opening of Chinese Markets</title>
<link>https://henix.github.io/feeds/bwdo/2018-03-27-bwam03272018.html</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bridgewater.com/resources/bwam03272018.pdf&quot;&gt;原文&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most global investors have very small allocations to China that do not appropriately reflect the size and importance of the Chinese economy or its assets.  We expect that will change significantly over the next few years, and we would encourage investors to think proactively about the exposure they want to China now.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<author>Bridgewater</author>
<guid isPermaLink="false">2018-03-27-bwam03272018</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>It’s All Classic: the Main Questions are About the Exact Timing and What the Next Downturn Will be Like</title>
<link>https://henix.github.io/feeds/bwdo/2018-02-12-bwam021218.html</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bridgewater.com/resources/bwam021218.pdf&quot;&gt;原文&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In these &lt;i&gt;Observations,&lt;/i&gt; we put what’s been happening in markets recently within the context of the classic short-term debt/business cycle.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<author>Bridgewater</author>
<guid isPermaLink="false">2018-02-12-bwam021218</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>How the World Is Changing: The Secular Picture</title>
<link>https://henix.github.io/feeds/bwdo/2018-01-12-bwam011218.html</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bridgewater.com/resources/bwam011218.pdf&quot;&gt;原文&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As we begin a new year, we wanted to step back and take stock of how unusually fast the global economy has changed over the past 15 years or so. Where growth is occurring and where wealth is held have moved so radically that relying on past market experiences to determine what is important to the global economy is particularly dangerous.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<author>Bridgewater</author>
<guid isPermaLink="false">2018-01-12-bwam011218</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Our Biggest Economic, Social and Political Issue; The Two Economies: The Top 40% and the Bottom 60%</title>
<link>https://henix.github.io/feeds/bwdo/2017-10-23-bwam102317.html</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bridgewater.com/resources/bwam102317.pdf&quot;&gt;原文&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;clamp-5 clamp-landscape-5&quot;&gt;Today, wealth and income skews are so great that average statistics no longer reflect the conditions of the majority of Americans. To give you a sense of what the picture below the averages looks like, we broke the economy into two economies—that of the top 40% and that of the bottom 60%.
&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<author>Bridgewater</author>
<guid isPermaLink="false">2017-10-23-bwam102317</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Opening of Chinese Credit Markets Means That Foreign Investors Can Build a Balanced Portfolio in China; This Will Be a Big Deal</title>
<link>https://henix.github.io/feeds/bwdo/2017-09-29-bwam09292017.html</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bridgewater.com/resources/bwam09292017.pdf&quot;&gt;原文&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;China is in the process of opening up and restructuring its capital markets, and its markets are on pace to become some of the most important liquid, publicly traded markets in the world. As the credit markets open up alongside the equity markets, there is a greater ability for investors to create balanced portfolios of Chinese assets.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<author>Bridgewater</author>
<guid isPermaLink="false">2017-09-29-bwam09292017</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Macro Implications of the Push Toward Electric Vehicles</title>
<link>https://henix.github.io/feeds/bwdo/2017-08-31-bwam083117.html</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bridgewater.com/resources/bwam083117.pdf&quot;&gt;原文&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The global push toward electric vehicles illustrates how technology can radically reshape entrenched industries (sectoral winners and losers), geopolitics (regional winners and losers), productivity, economic growth, and of course demand for extractive commodities (particularly oil). Today’s &lt;i&gt;Observations&lt;/i&gt; looks at the implications for growth and oil demand.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<author>Bridgewater</author>
<guid isPermaLink="false">2017-08-31-bwam083117</guid>
<pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Populism: The Phenomenon</title>
<link>https://henix.github.io/feeds/bwdo/2017-03-22-bwam032217.html</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bridgewater.com/resources/bwam032217.pdf&quot;&gt;原文&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This report is an examination of populism, the phenomenon—how it typically germinates, grows, and runs its course.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<author>Bridgewater</author>
<guid isPermaLink="false">2017-03-22-bwam032217</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>Understanding the High Returns in a Low Return Environment</title>
<link>https://henix.github.io/feeds/bwdo/2017-03-14-bwam031417.html</link>
<description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bridgewater.com/resources/bwam031417.pdf&quot;&gt;原文&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since the global financial crisis, most global asset portfolios have performed extremely well, and we are worried that this performance is creating complacency about future returns. While backward-looking returns of a traditional portfolio are near all-time highs, forward-looking expected returns are near all-time lows.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<author>Bridgewater</author>
<guid isPermaLink="false">2017-03-14-bwam031417</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
